<contract><section><section_name> have reviewed with Selling Dealer 
the sections of this Service Contract titled: SERVICE CONTRACT COVERAGE, VEHICLE COVERED PARTS, 
SERVICE CONTRACT PERIOD, EXCLUSIONS FROM COVERAGE, YOUR RESPONSIBILITIES, HOW TO 
</section_name><subsection_name>SERVICE COMPANY AND ADMINISTRATOR
</subsection_name></section><section><section_name>VEHICLE COVERED PARTS
</section_name><subsection_name>POWERTRAIN COVERAGE PLAN
</subsection_name></section><section><section_name>POWERTRAIN COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>ENGINE</subsection_name><description> Engine block and cylinder heads and all internally lubricated parts including pistons, piston rings, pins and cylinder sleeves; 
crankshaft, pulley, main bearings, caps and bolts; connecting rods, rod bearings, caps and bolts; camshaft(s), camshaft bearings, 
buttons and plugs; timing gears and timing chain or belt; rocker arms, rocker arm pivots, shafts and bushings; intake and exhaust 
valves, springs, guides, adjusters, retainers and seats; pushrods and lifters; intake manifold; exhaust manifolds; balance shaft; water 
pump; fuel pump; thermostat; oil pump, cover, gears, pressure relief valve and screen; rotor housing, rotors, shims and silent shaft; 
all internal fasteners, nuts and bolts; turbocharger/supercharger assembly including boost valve and wastegate; seals and gaskets.
</description></section><section><section_name>SILVER COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>STEERING</subsection_name><description> Steering gear housing and internal parts including control rings, valves, pinion shaft, pitman shaft, worm shaft and gear, 
sector shaft, bearings, adjusters; rack and pinion housing and internal parts including control valve, rack bellows, mounts, rack shaft 
and yoke, spool valve, bearings; power steering pump and internal parts including housing, reservoir, shaft and vanes; power steering 
pump mounting brackets; seals and gaskets.
</description></section><section><section_name>GOLD COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>ENGINE</subsection_name><description> Oil pan; valve, timing and side covers; thermostat housing; water pump pulley; engine mounts; harmonic balancer; &#64258; ex 
plate/&#64258; ywheel and ring gear.
</description><subsection_name>TRANSMISSION</subsection_name><description> Oil pan; detent cable; kickdown link; TVI/throttle cable; vacuum modulator; transmission mounts.
</description><subsection_name>DRIVE AXLE</subsection_name><description> Constant velocity joints; slip joint; front wheel drive axles/half-shafts and wheel bearings; u-joints; couplings; &#64258; ex disc; 
prop shafts; center support bearings.
</description><subsection_name>STEERING</subsection_name><description> Tie rods, idler and pitman arms, center/drag link, coupling and shafts; cooler lines.
</description><subsection_name>BRAKES</subsection_name><description> Compensator/proportioning valve; metering valve; calipers, piston, seal and dust boot; wheel cylinders, cups, seals, spring 
and dust boots; backing plate; brake adjusters; brake pedal, pedal lever and pedal pivot; parking brake cable; ABS component parts 
including control processor/module, pump, dump valve, wheel speed sensors, solenoids, accumulator, and pressure differential switch.
</description><subsection_name>AIR CONDITIONING</subsection_name><description> Accumulator; receiver drier; automatic temperature control programmer; clutch assembly including coil, disc 
and pulley; control cables; cutoff switch; serpentine belt tensioner, bearing and pulley.
</description><subsection_name>FRONT SUSPENSION</subsection_name><description> Wheel bearings; ball joints and bushings; kingpin and bushings; stabilizer bar, links and bushings; torsion 
bar, mounts and bushings; track bar, links and bushings.
</description><subsection_name>ELECTRICAL</subsection_name><description> Front and rear wiper motor, transmission and linkage; power window motor; window regulators; power seat motor; 
steering column multi-function switch and individual switches for turn signal, headlamp, dimmer, wiper, washer and speed control; 
mirror motor switch; brake light switch; neutral safety switch; glove box light switch; courtesy light switch; cooling fan relay; air 
control solenoid; air regulator valve; I.A.C. motor; electronic ignition module; electronic instrument panel module; ignition coil; engine 
distributor including shaft, gear, bushings and modules; throttle position sensor; vehicle speed sensor; M.A.P. sensor; knock sensor 
and barometric pressure sensor.
</description><subsection_name>ADDITIONAL HYBRID/PLUG-IN ELECTRIC/COMPRESSED NATURAL GAS COMPONENTS</subsection_name><description> Motor/generator belt tensioner; 
drive motor dampener; voltage inverter reservoir; three-phase high voltage cables; hydraulic or electric regenerative braking system; 
seals and gaskets for the above listed components.
</description></section><section><section_name>GOLD PLUS COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>COOLING</subsection_name><description> Radiator, mounting brackets and coolant recovery tank; fan clutch, fan blades and motor; fan shroud; heater core; 
transmission cooler.
</description><subsection_name>FUEL</subsection_name><description> Fuel lines; fuel pressure regulator; level sending unit; fuel injectors and seals; injection pump; ESC systems; fuel injection 
control components including mixture control processor, throttle body assembly, cutoff valve, fuel rail, fuel distributor, trigger contacts, 
cold start valve, fuel injection valve, fuel accumulator; tank; tank door latch; tank &#64257; ller neck and o-ring.
</description><subsection_name>AIR CONDITIONING</subsection_name><description> Compressor mounting brackets; idler pulley and bearings; air conditioning/heater blower motor.
</description><subsection_name>STEERING</subsection_name><description> Steering wheel tilt and telescoping mechanism.
</description><subsection_name>FRONT SUSPENSION</subsection_name><description> Coil and leaf springs, seats and bushings, leaf spring shackles; electronic level control components including 
</description><subsection_name>pump, accumulator, lines and bags.
</subsection_name><description>REAR SUSPENSION:</description><subsection_name> Upper and lower control arms, shafts and bushings; upper and lower ball joints; struts, housing and cartridge; 
wheel bearings; spindle/steering knuckle and spindle support; coil and leaf springs, seats and bushings, leaf spring shackles; track bars, 
links and bushings; electronic level control components including pump, accumulator, lines, bags; stabilizer bar, links and bushings.
</subsection_name><description>ELECTRICAL:</description></section><section><section_name>PLATINUM COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>Includes the Powertrain, Silver, Gold and Gold Plus Coverage Plans plus ANY OTHER MECHANICAL BREAKDOWN except for 
those items listed in the sections </subsection_name><description>&#8220;EXCLUSIONS FROM COVERAGE&#8221;</description><subsection_name> and </subsection_name><description>&#8220;LIMITS OF LIABILITY.&#8221;</description><subsection_name> All other terms and conditions 
of this Service Contract remain unchanged.
</subsection_name></section><section><section_name> 14. UNDER PLATINUM COVERAGE, ANY OF THE FOLLOWING PARTS: BRAKE LININGS, BRAKE DRUMS AND ROTORS, 
DISC BRAKE PADS, STANDARD TRANSMISSION CLUTCH COMPONENTS AND ASSEMBLIES, AIR BAGS, SOLAR 
POWERED DEVICES, HINGES, GLASS, LENSES, SEALED BEAMS, BODY PARTS AND/OR PANELS, TRIM, MOLDINGS, 
DOOR HANDLES, LOCK CYLINDERS, TIRES, WHEELS, ALL BATTERIES EXCEPT HYBRID/EV/HIGH VOLTAGE 
BATTERIES AS LISTED UNDER SILVER COVERAGE PLAN, LIGHT BULBS, UPHOLSTERY, PAINT, BRIGHT METAL, 
FREEZE PLUGS, HEATER AND RADIATOR HOSES, EXHAUST SYSTEM, SHOCK ABSORBERS, AUDIO/SECURITY OR 
OTHER SYSTEMS NOT FACTORY INSTALLED, WORK SUCH AS FRONT-END ALIGNMENT OR WHEEL BALANCING, 
CONSTANT VELOCITY JOINT BOOTS, SAFETY RESTRAINT SYSTEMS, CELLULAR PHONES, RADAR DETECTORS, 
APPLIANCES, OR VINYL AND CONVERTIBLE TOPS;
</section_name><subsection_name> 15. GRADUAL BATTERY CAPACITY LOSS. NICKEL-METAL HYDRATE OR LITHIUM-ION BATTERIES, LIKE ALL BATTERIES, 
WILL EXPERIENCE GRADUAL CAPACITY LOSS WITH TIME AND USE. LOSS OF BATTERY CAPACITY DUE TO OR 
RESULTING FROM GRADUAL CAPACITY LOSS IS NOT COVERED UNDER THIS SERVICE CONTRACT;
</subsection_name></section></contract>