<contract><section><section_name>have reviewed with Selling Dealer
the sections of this Service Contract titled: SERVICE CONTRACT COVERAGE, VEHICLE COVERED PARTS,
</section_name><subsection_name>FIDELITY WARRANTY SERVICES, INC.
</subsection_name></section><section><section_name>have reviewed with Selling Dealer
the sections of this Service Contract titled: SERVICE CONTRACT COVERAGE, VEHICLE COVERED PARTS,
</section_name><subsection_name>FIDELITY WARRANTY SERVICES, INC.
</subsection_name></section><section><section_name>VEHICLE COVERED PARTS
</section_name><subsection_name>POWERTRAIN COVERAGE PLAN
</subsection_name></section><section><section_name>POWERTRAIN COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>ENGINE</subsection_name><description> Engine block and cylinder heads and all internally lubricated parts including pistons, piston rings, pins and cylinder sleeves;
crankshaft, pulley, main bearings, caps and bolts; connecting rods, rod bearings, caps and bolts; camshaft(s), camshaft bearings,
buttons and plugs; timing gears and timing chain or belt; rocker arms, rocker arm pivots, shafts and bushings; intake and exhaust valves,
springs, guides, adjusters, retainers and seats; pushrods and lifters; intake manifold; exhaust manifolds; balance shaft; water pump;
fuel pump; thermostat; oil pump, cover, gears, pressure relief valve and screen; rotor housing, rotors, shims and silent shaft; all internal
fasteners, nuts and bolts; turbocharger/supercharger assembly including boost valve and wastegate; seals and gaskets.
</description><subsection_name>TRANSMISSION/TRANSAXLE/TRANSFER CASE</subsection_name><description> Transmission/transaxle case and all internally lubricated parts including ring and
pinion gears; oil pump, cover, gears, housing and vanes; torque converter; valve body(s); throttle valve; valve pack; governor, gear
and cover; parking gear and pawl; roll pins; sprags; sprockets; chain; springs; stator and shaft; pressure regulator valve; pressure
switches; solenoids; bands; automatic transmission/transaxle clutch, drums, pistons and steel plates; planetary and sun gears; servos
and rings; blockers; synchronizer hubs and keys; bearings; bushings; supports and shafts; control rings; yoke; extension housing;
speedometer drive gears; accumulators and rings; adjusters; all internal fasteners, nuts and bolts; shift cover and forks; separate bell
housing; transfer case and all internal parts contained within the transfer case; seals and gaskets. </description><subsection_name>(STANDARD TRANSMISSION
CLUTCH ASSEMBLIES AND ALL COMPONENT PARTS ARE NOT COVERED.)
DRIVE AXLE</subsection_name><description> Differential/axle housing(s) and all internally lubricated parts including the axle flange; ring and pinion gear/carrier
assembly; spider gears and bearings; pins; retainers; positraction clutches, plates and springs; cover; seals and gaskets.
</description></section><section><section_name>SILVER COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>STEERING</subsection_name><description> Steering gear housing and internal parts including control rings, valves, pinion shaft, pitman shaft, worm shaft and gear,
sector shaft, bearings, adjusters; rack and pinion housing and internal parts including control valve, rack bellows, mounts, rack shaft
and yoke, spool valve, bearings; power steering pump and internal parts including housing, reservoir, shaft and vanes; power steering
pump mounting brackets; seals and gaskets.
</description><subsection_name>BRAKES</subsection_name><description> Master cylinder; vacuum or hydraulic brake booster assembly; hydraulic lines, hoses and fittings; brake pedal apply pin;
seals and gaskets. </description><subsection_name>(ABS COMPONENTS NOT COVERED.)
AIR CONDITIONING</subsection_name><description> Condensor; compressor; evaporator; orifice/expansion; seals and gaskets.
</description><subsection_name>FRONT SUSPENSION</subsection_name><description> Upper and lower control arms, shafts and bushings; struts, housing and cartridge; spindle/steering knuckle
and spindle support.
</description><subsection_name>ELECTRICAL</subsection_name><description> Alternator housing and all internal parts including bearings, bushings, brushes, rectifier bridge, diodes, field coil and
rotor; alternator mounting bracket; voltage regulator; starter motor housing and all internal parts including bushings, brushes, field
windings, starter drive and solenoid.
</description></section><section><section_name>GOLD COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>ENGINE</subsection_name><description> Oil pan; valve, timing and side covers; thermostat housing; water pump pulley; engine mounts; harmonic balancer; flex plate/
flywheel and ring gear.
</description><subsection_name>TRANSMISSION</subsection_name><description> Oil pan; detent cable; kickdown link; TVI/throttle cable; vacuum modulator; transmission mounts.
</description><subsection_name>DRIVE AXLE</subsection_name><description> Constant velocity joints; slip joint; front wheel drive axles/halfshafts and wheel bearings; u-joints; couplings; flex disc;
</description><subsection_name>prop shafts; center support bearings.
</subsection_name><description>STEERING:</description><subsection_name> Tie rods, idler and pitman arms, center/drag link, coupling and shafts; cooler lines.
</subsection_name><description>BRAKES:</description><subsection_name> Compensator/proportioning valve; metering valve; calipers, piston, seal and dust boot; wheel cylinders, cups, seals, spring
and dust boots; backing plate; brake adjusters; brake pedal, pedal lever and pedal pivot; parking brake cable; ABS component parts
including control processor/module, pump, dump valve, wheel speed sensors, solenoids, accumulator, and pressure differential switch.
</subsection_name><description>AIR CONDITIONING:</description><subsection_name> Accumulator; receiver drier; automatic temperature control programmer; clutch assembly including coil, disc and
pulley; control cables; cutoff switch; serpentine belt tensioner, bearing and pulley.
</subsection_name><description>FRONT SUSPENSION: </description><subsection_name>Wheel bearings; ball joints and bushings; kingpin and bushings; stabilizer bar, links and bushings; torsion bar,
mounts and bushings; track bar, links and bushings.
</subsection_name><description>ELECTRICAL:</description><subsection_name> Front and rear wiper motor, transmission and linkage; power window motor; window regulators; power seat motor;
steering column multi-function switch and individual switches for turn signal, headlamp, dimmer, wiper, washer and speed control;
mirror motor switch; brake light switch; neutral safety switch; glove box light switch; courtesy light switch; cooling fan relay; air control
solenoid; air regulator valve; I.A.C. motor; electronic ignition module; electronic instrument panel module; ignition coil; engine distributor
</subsection_name><description>including shaft, gear, bushings and modules; throttle position sensor; vehicle speed sensor; M.A.P. sensor; knock sensor and
barometric pressure sensor.
</description></section><section><section_name>GOLD PLUS COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>COOLING</subsection_name><description> Radiator, mounting brackets and coolant recovery tank; fan clutch, fan blades and motor; fan shroud; heater core;
transmission cooler.
</description><subsection_name>FUEL</subsection_name><description> Fuel lines; fuel pressure regulator; level sending unit; fuel injectors and seals; injection pump; ESC systems; fuel injection control
components including mixture control processor, throttle body assembly, cutoff valve, fuel rail, fuel distributor, trigger contacts, cold
start valve, fuel injection valve, fuel accumulator; tank; tank door latch; tank filler neck and o-ring.
</description><subsection_name>AIR CONDITIONING</subsection_name><description> Compressor mounting brackets; idler pulley and bearings; air conditioning/heater blower motor.
</description><subsection_name>STEERING</subsection_name><description> Steering wheel tilt and telescoping mechanism.
</description><subsection_name>FRONT SUSPENSION</subsection_name><description> Coil and leaf springs, seats and bushings, leaf spring shackles; electronic level control components including
pump, accumulator, lines and bags.
</description><subsection_name>REAR SUSPENSION</subsection_name><description> Upper and lower control arms, shafts and bushings; upper and lower ball joints; struts, housing and cartridge;
wheel bearings; spindle/steering knuckle and spindle support; coil and leaf springs, seats and bushings, leaf spring shackles; track bars,
links and bushings; electronic level control components including pump, accumulator, lines, bags; stabilizer bar, links and bushings.
</description><subsection_name>ELECTRICAL</subsection_name><description> Cruise control module, servo, cables and switches; instrument cluster including speedometer, odometer, tachometer
and all gauges, warning indicators; burglar alarm or electronic entry systems including remote entry receiver, sender and module; door
lock actuators; mirror motor; power window switch; power lock switch; rear window defogger; horn and relay; convertible top motor;
sunroof motor; power antenna motor; electrical headlamp motor; power trunk/hatch release motor, switch and solenoid; power sliding
door motor and switch; electronic control modules including body control module, electronic control unit, powertrain control module,
transmission control module; electronic throttle control module; crank angle sensor; camshaft position sensor; throttle position motor;
fuel pulse dampener; wide open throttle switch; thermo time switch; fuel pump relay; automatic temperature control sensor; ride height
sensor and relay; oxygen (02) sensor; mass air flow sensor; manifold differential pressure sensor; coolant temperature sensor; OEM
radio/graphic equalizer/cassette tape player/compact disc player.
</description></section><section><section_name>PLATINUM COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>Includes the Powertrain, Silver, Gold and Gold Plus coverage plans plus ANY OTHER MECHANICAL BREAKDOWN except for those
items listed in the sections </subsection_name><description>&#8220;EXCLUSIONS FROM COVERAGE&#8221;,</description><subsection_name> and the section </subsection_name><description>&#8220;LIMITS OF LIABILITY.&#8221;</description><subsection_name> All other terms and
conditions of this Service Contract remain unchanged.
</subsection_name></section><section><section_name>14. UNDER PLATINUM COVERAGE, ANY OF THE FOLLOWING PARTS: BRAKE LININGS, BRAKE DRUMS AND ROTORS,
DISC BRAKE PADS, STANDARD TRANSMISSION CLUTCH COMPONENTS, AIR BAGS, SOLAR POWERED DEVICES,
HINGES, GLASS, LENSES, SEALED BEAMS, BODY PARTS AND/OR PANELS, TRIM, MOLDINGS, DOOR HANDLES,
LOCK CYLINDERS, TIRES, WHEELS, BATTERIES, LIGHT BULBS, UPHOLSTERY, PAINT, BRIGHT METAL, FREEZE
PLUGS, HEATER AND RADIATOR HOSES, EXHAUST SYSTEM, SHOCK ABSORBERS, AUDIO, SECURITY OR OTHER
SYSTEMS NOT FACTORY INSTALLED, WORK SUCH AS FRONT-END ALIGNMENT OR WHEEL BALANCING, CONSTANT
VELOCITY JOINT BOOTS, SAFETY RESTRAINT SYSTEMS, CELLULAR PHONES, ELECTRONIC TRANSMITTING
DEVICES (EXCEPT FOR THOSE SPECIFICALLY LISTED UNDER SILVER, GOLD, OR GOLD PLUS COVERAGE), RADAR
DETECTORS, APPLIANCES, NEAR OBJECT AVOIDANCE SYSTEMS AND ALL LASER RADAR CRUISE CONTROL
COMPONENTS, VINYL AND CONVERTIBLE TOPS;
</section_name><subsection_name>15. BURNT VALVES, WORN PISTON RINGS, THE CORRECTION OF OIL CONSUMPTION, ANY REPAIRS FOR REDUCTION
</subsection_name></section></contract>