<contract><section><section_name> have reviewed with Selling
Dealer the sections of this Service Contract
titled: SERVICE CONTRACT COVERAGE,
VEHICLE COVERED PARTS, SERVICE
CONTRACT PERIOD, EXCLUSIONS FROM
COVERAGE, HOW TO MAKE A CLAIM,
CANCELLATION, DEDUCTIBLE AND
UNCOVERED COSTS and IMPLIED
WARRANTY.
</section_name><subsection_name>24/30,000
</subsection_name></section><section><section_name>POWERTRAIN COVERAGE
</section_name><subsection_name>VEHICLE COVERED PARTS:</subsection_name><description>ENGINE: Engine block and cylinder heads and all internally lubricated parts in-</description><subsection_name>stator and shaft; pressure regulator valve; pressure switches; solenoids; bands;</subsection_name><description>automatic transmission/transaxle clutch, drums, pistons and steel plates; plan-</description><subsection_name>(includes POWERTRAIN coverage plus the following additional parts)</subsection_name><description /></section><section><section_name>VEHICLE COVERED PARTS:
ENGINE:</section_name><subsection_name>stator and shaft; pressure regulator valve; pressure switches; solenoids; bands;
automatic transmission/transaxle clutch, drums, pistons and steel plates; plan-
etary and sun gears; servos and rings; blockers; synchronizer hubs and keys;
bearings; bushings; supports and shafts; control rings; yoke; extension housing;
speedometer drive gears; accumulators and rings; adjusters; all internal fasten-
ers, nuts and bolts; shift cover and forks; separate bell housing; seals and gas-
kets. </subsection_name><description>(STANDARD TRANSMISSION CLUTCH ASSEMBLIES AND ALL COM-
PONENT PARTS ARE NOT COVERED.)
DRIVE AXLE:</description><subsection_name> Differential/axle housing(s) and all internal parts contained within
the differential/axle housing(s) including the axle flange; ring and pinion gear/car-
rier assembly; spider gears and bearings; pins; retainers; positraction clutches,
plates and springs; cover. Transfer case and all internal parts contained within the
transfer case. Seals and gaskets.
</subsection_name></section><section><section_name>SILVER COVERAGE
</section_name><subsection_name>ENGINE: Oil pan; valve, timing and side covers; thermostat housing; water pump</subsection_name><description>pulley; turbocharger/supercharger assembly including boost valve and wastegate;</description><subsection_name>sor/module, pump, dump valve, wheel speed sensors, solenoids, accumulator,</subsection_name><description>pressure differential switch; seals and gaskets.</description><subsection_name>(includes POWERTRAIN and SILVER coverage plus the following additional parts)</subsection_name><description /></section><section><section_name>GOLD COVERAGE
</section_name><subsection_name>TRANSMISSION/TRANSAXLE: Oil pan</subsection_name><description>COOLING: Radiator, mounting brackets and coolant recovery tank; fan clutch,</description><subsection_name>steering knuckle and spindle support; coil or leaf springs, seats or bushings, leaf</subsection_name><description>spring shackles; track bars, links and bushings; electronic level control compo-</description></section><section><section_name>PLATINUM COVERAGE
</section_name><subsection_name>Includes the Powertrain, Silver and Gold coverage plans plus ANY OTHER MECHANICAL BREAKDOWN except for those items listed in the sections "EXCLUSIONS</subsection_name><description>FROM COVERAGE", and the section "LIMITS OF LIABILITY." All other terms and conditions of this Service Contract remain unchanged.</description><subsection_name>A-100 (04/01)</subsection_name><description>Page 2 of 5</description><subsection_name /></section><section><section_name>12. LIABILITY FOR DAMAGE TO PROPERTY, INJURY TO OR DEATH OF ANY PERSON ARISING OUT OF THE
OPERATION, MAINTENANCE OR USE OF YOUR VEHICLE WHETHER OR NOT RELATED TO THE COVERED PARTS;
13. UNDER POWERTRAIN, SILVER, AND GOLD COVERAGES, ANY PART THAT IS NOT SPECIFICALLY LISTED AS
</section_name><subsection_name>COVERED UNDER THE COVERAGE SELECTED;
</subsection_name></section><section><section_name>14. UNDER PLATINUM COVERAGE, ANY OF THE FOLLOWING PARTS: BRAKE LININGS, BRAKE DRUMS AND
ROTORS, DISC BRAKE PADS, STANDARD TRANSMISSION CLUTCH COMPONENTS, AIR BAGS, SOLAR POW-
ERED DEVICES, HINGES, GLASS, LENSES, SEALED BEAMS, TRIM, MOLDINGS, DOOR HANDLES, LOCK CYLIN-
DERS, TIRES, BATTERIES, LIGHT BULBS, UPHOLSTERY, PAINT, BRIGHT METAL, HEADBOLTS, FREEZE PLUGS,
EXHAUST SYSTEM, SHOCK ABSORBERS, RUST AND RUST DAMAGE, AUDIO, SECURITY OR OTHER SYSTEMS
NOT FACTORY INSTALLED, WORK SUCH AS FRONT-END ALIGNMENT OR WHEEL BALANCING, CONSTANT
VELOCITY JOINT BOOTS, SAFETY RESTRAINT SYSTEMS, CELLULAR PHONES, TELEVISION/VCR, ELECTRONIC
TRANSMITTING DEVICES, RADAR DETECTORS, APPLIANCES, NAVIGATION/NEAR OBJECT AVOIDANCE SYS-
</section_name><subsection_name>15. BURNT VALVES, WORN RINGS, THE CORRECTION OF OIL CONSUMPTION, ANY REPAIRS FOR REDUCTION IN
</subsection_name></section></contract>