<contract><section><section_name>SILVER COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>ENGINE
</subsection_name><description>Engine block and cylinder heads and internal parts including pistons, piston rings and pins; crankshaft, mainbearings, rods and rod bearings; camshaft(s) and camshaft bearings; timing
gears and timing chain or belt; rocker arms, shafts and bushings; valves and valve springs, guides and seats; pushrods and lifters; oil pump, intake and exhaust manifolds; engine
mounts, balancer and flywheel. Engine seals and gaskets, water pump.
</description><subsection_name>FUEL
</subsection_name><description>Fuel supply pump, return lines, fuel pressure regulator.
</description><subsection_name>AIR CONDITIONING*
</subsection_name><description>Condensor, compressor, evaporator core, seals and gaskets.
</description><subsection_name>AUTOMATIC TRANSMISSION/TRANSAXLE
</subsection_name><description>Automatic transmission case and all internal parts including torque converter, ring and pinion gears, sun gear, planetary gear and internal bearings and seals and gaskets.
</description><subsection_name>MANUAL TRANSMISSION/TRANSAXLE
</subsection_name><description>Manual transmission/transaxle housing and all internal parts including ring and pinion gears, sun gear, planetary gear, synchros, shift rails, internal bearings; seals and gaskets (Clutch
and all clutch components are not covered).
</description><subsection_name>STEERING
</subsection_name><description>Steering gear housing and internal parts; rack and pinion housing and internal parts; power steering pump, seals and gaskets.
</description><subsection_name>SUSPENSION </subsection_name><description>(Front and Rear)
Control arms, shafts and bushings; upper and lower ball joints; struts, wheel bearings, spindle and spindle support.
</description><subsection_name>DRIVE AXLE
</subsection_name><description>Parts contained within front or rear differential/axle housings and transfer case and internal parts including drive shafts, axle shafts, bearings, u-joints and constant velocity joints; seals
and gaskets.
</description><subsection_name>BRAKES
</subsection_name><description>Master cylinder and booster; compensator or proportioning valve; brake lines, ABS component parts.
</description><subsection_name>ELECTRICAL
</subsection_name><description>Generator or alternator, voltage regulator; starter motor, solenoid and drive; wiper, window and seat motors; engine distributor and module.
</description></section><section><section_name>GOLD COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>(includes Silver coverage plus the following additional parts)
</subsection_name></section><section><section_name>PLATINUM COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>Includes the Silver and Gold coverage plans plus ANY OTHER MECHANICAL BREAKDOWN except for those items listed in the sections</subsection_name><description> "Exclusions From Coverage," </description><subsection_name>and the section
</subsection_name><description>"Limits of Liability." </description><subsection_name>All other terms and conditions of the contract remain unchanged.
</subsection_name></section></contract>