<contract><section><section_name>USED VEHICLE COVERED PARTS
POWERTRAIN COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>ENGINE</subsection_name><description> Engine block and cylinder heads and all internally
lubricated parts including pistons, piston rings, pins and cylinder
sleeves; crankshaft, pulley, mainbearings, caps and bolts;
connecting rods, rod bearings, caps and bolts; camshaft(s),
camshaft bearings, buttons and plugs; timing gears and timing
chain or belt; rocker arms, rocker arm pivots, shafts and bushings;
intake and exhaust valves, springs, guides, adjusters, retainers
and seats; pushrods and lifters; intake manifold and exhaust
manifolds; balance shaft; water pump; fuel pump; thermostat; oil
pump, cover, gears, pressure relief valve and screen; rotor housing,
rotors, shims and silent shaft; all internal fasteners, nuts and bolts;
seals and gaskets.
</description><subsection_name>TRANSMISSION/TRANSAXLE </subsection_name><description>Transmission/Transaxle case
and all internally lubricated parts including ring and pinion gears;
oil pump, cover, gears, housing and vanes; torque converter; valve
body(s); throttle valve; valve pack; governor, gear and cover;
parking gear and pawl; roll pins; sprags; sprockets; chain; springs;
</description></section><section><section_name>SILVER COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>STEERING</subsection_name><description> Steering gear housing and internal parts including
control rings, valves, pinion shaft, pitman shaft, worm shaft and
gear, sector shaft, bearings, adjusters; rack and pinion housing
and internal parts including control valve, rack bellows, mounts,
rack shaft and yoke, spool valve, bearings; power steering pump
and internal parts including housing, reservoir, shaft and vanes;
pump mounting brackets; seals and gaskets.
</description><subsection_name>BRAKES</subsection_name><description> Master cylinder; vacuum or hydraulic brake booster
assembly; hydraulic lines and fittings; brake pedal apply pin; seals
and gaskets. </description><subsection_name>(ABS COMPONENTS NOT COVERED).
</subsection_name></section><section><section_name>GOLD COVERAGE PLAN
</section_name><subsection_name>ENGINE</subsection_name><description> Oil pan; valve, timing and side covers; thermostat
housing; water pump pulley; turbocharger/supercharger assembly
including boost valve and wastegate; engine mounts; harmonic
balancer; flexplate/flywheel and ring gear.
</description><subsection_name>TRANSMISSION</subsection_name><description> Detent cable; kickdown link; TVI/throttle cable;
vacuum modulator; transmission mounts.
</description><subsection_name>DRIVE AXLE</subsection_name><description> Constant velocity joints; slip joint; front wheel drive
axles/halfshafts and wheel bearings; u-joints; couplings; flex disc;
propshafts; center support bearings.
</description><subsection_name>STEERING</subsection_name><description> Tie rods, idler and pitman arms, center/drag link,
coupling and shafts; cooler lines.
</description><subsection_name>BRAKES </subsection_name><description>Compensator or proportioning valve and metering valve;
Calipers, piston, seal and dust boot; wheel cylinders, cups, seals,
spring and dust boots; backing plate; brake adjusters; brake pedal,
pedal lever and pedal pivot. </description><subsection_name>(ABS COMPONENTS NOT COVERED).
</subsection_name></section></contract>